to having sex with my ex last week my ex GF twenty called and asked if
I twenty to M was keen to continue sleeping with her I never expected to hear
from her again let alone see her naked our relationship recently came to an end I
tapped out because it became clear to me that the two of us were incompatible my
ex disagreed and thought screaming at me would somehow change my opinion considering how upset she
was during our breakup I was surprised when I got the call from her asking for
sex she said she had no intention of getting back together all she wanted was to
share a bed with someone who knew her well enough to know what buttons to press
to get her off not gonna lie the unexpected ego boost disarmed me her closing comment
was scratch out the friends and friends with benefits but keep the benefits I was willing
to test it out last night my ex and I reunited for the first time since
the dramatic final episode of our relationship she followed me to my room and we hooked
up I woke up this morning with one arm cuff to my bed my ex was
gone a random note on the pillow said the key for the handcuffs was in the
condom under the pillow I flipped the pillow and discovered the condom a used condom but
not the condom I used different brand different size different load I did what had to
be done to get the key out of the condiment unlocked the handcuffs it was like
a fear factor challenge but all you get his some dude's not juice on your fingers
without wasting time I disposed of the condom the key the cuffs and the pillow before
tossing all my sheets in the laundry and scrubbing my hands with disinfectant I was fuming
but I was prepared to file my experience under crazy x GF and never communicate with
my ex again however I soon realized she did more than plant another person's used condom
under my pillow she planted another person's used condom in one of my running shoes as
well the condom actually stuck to the bottom of my foot when I removed my shoe
it was disgusting I decided to check everything shoes socks pockets bags etc I managed to
find another used condom in the hood of my hoodie I informed my room made because
I didn't know if my ex was crazy enough to hide used condoms elsewhere in our
flat he advised me to block and delete her phone number and social media which is
what I did my room mate and I have been searching for used condoms in every
corner of our flat since we got out of bed I have so many questions are
all those condoms from the same person does that person know my ex was using safe
sex for evil how did I not see this level of crazy during my relationship I
guess I'll never know TL de are I allowed my ex GF to convince me to
sleep with her and now I'm discovering used condoms that she planted in my room to
demonstrate how much she hates me